

PROFILE

Hello Everyone! I welcome you all in my official resume paper. To introduce myself, recently I have been studying Bachelor of Information Technology at Phoenix College of Management. I have one year of working experiences as a **Data Analyst** and **Data Manager** at one of the reputed E-commerce Website namely **Online Saathi**. In the field of IT, I have good skills and knowledge of following programs.

CONTACT

PHONE:

+977 9816246451

WEBSITE:

kshitiz58.github.io/babik37

EMAIL:

kshitizbabik.37@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Programming Photography Designing Reading Novel

KSHITIJ BISHOKARMA

Student

Bachelor of Information Technology Phoenix College of Management Kathmandu, Nepal (Lincoln University Affiliates)

EDUCATION

Mount Everest School

2010 - 2017

I have completed my secondary level of education from my own birth place namely Chandrapur-3, Rautahat with GPA 3.55(A)s

Liverpool Int'l College

2017 – 2019

I have completed my 10+2 level of education choosing major subject 'Biology' from Science faculty in Kathmandu with GPA 2.97(B+).

WORK EXPERIENCE

Softech Solution [File Manager]

2019

I have worked around 4 months here and my main job is to handle all the data and file and place it in the systematic order.

Online Saathi [Data Analyst]

2020-2021

I have to analyze all the website data with comparison to other e- commerce websites. I have to also guide other team member in price fixing in new entry product.

Seshra Innovation [Website Design]

2021-Present

I have done internship for around 6 months in Graphics and Website Design and make myself able to design basic designs.

SKILLS

